<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>Abhay's Blog</title>
    
    
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Adding Two Numbers</title>
        <description>
          What goes inside A Computer - 
          Abstractions are everywhere and that’s because they are very useful. They hide the complexity and allow us to focus on important aspects of problem/situation. Object oriented programming, Operating Systems and multiple branches of Mathematics essentially use powerful abstractions. In order to reason about them, we use the properties that has...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-10-23-Adding-Two-Numbers/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-10-23-Adding-Two-Numbers/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lambda Calculas</title>
        <description>
          Principle of Programming languages - 
          Untyped Lambda Calculas Syntax t := x variable |λx.t Abstraction |t t Application Reducing the no of parenthesis λx.t1 t2 t3 == λx.(t1 t2 t3) t1 t2 t3 == (t1 t2) t3 : Associate to the left λx y z.t == λx.(λy.(λz.t)) Free and Bound Variables Occurence of x inside...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-09-05-Lambda-Calculas-Notes/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-09-05-Lambda-Calculas-Notes/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Getting LLVM from Source</title>
        <description>
          Minimize Build time and space usage. - 
          LLVM-Project comprises of many low-level utilities, The most important of which is llvm core. LLVM core is a big piece of software and when combined with additional packages which are part of LLVM-project. like clang and lld, The complete build size can reach up to 70-80 GB. In case you...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-05-27-LLVM-Installation-Guide/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-05-27-LLVM-Installation-Guide/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Prophet</title>
        <description>
          Khalil Gibran - 
          “The Prophet”, A collection of poems written by Khalil Gibran. The Prophet is a person who lived in the city for 7 years waiting for A ship to come which will take him to his Home ( A metaphor ). Finally Ship has arrived And while Prophet Plans for departure,...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-05-14-The-Prophet/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-05-14-The-Prophet/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How I build a simple static site</title>
        <description>
          Use beautiful-jekyll template - 
          This is my first post and a test post. I will try some different things so bear with me if they get not-so-interesting. I will go step by step on how the whole process was completed. I am on Ubuntu 20.04.Using bash terminal. Steps for generating simple static site Note:...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-04-05-Building-a-static-site/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-04-05-Building-a-static-site/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>INVICTUS</title>
        <description>
          William Ernest Henley - 
          While spending his days in Robben Isand Prison, Nelson Mandela used to recite a poem by the 18th century English poet, William Ernest Henley. This poem inspired him and other prison mates to stay put and keep going through the hard times. Out of the night that covers me Black...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2021-04-01-invictus/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2021-04-01-invictus/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
